Introducing ICICI Pro Gift Select, a
plan offering long-term guaranteed
income up to 40 years with income
starting as early as first year. With
ICICI Pro Gift Select, you have the
flexibility to choose your policy term.
You can also choose your premium payment
term to match your financial goals. Get
an option to choose up to 50% instant
cash back on your first premium paid.
Decide when you want to start receiving
your income as early as the first year
or later. This plan also lets you tailor
your income by offering two flexible
income options.
With level income, you receive a fixed
amount every year throughout the policy
term. With increasing income, your
payouts grow by 5% every year on a
compounding basis.
Both options provide life cover for the
entire duration of the policy.
[Music]
Enjoy additional benefits like up to
200% return of premiums paid as maturity
benefit, flexible income periods, tax
benefits on both premiums paid and
returns received and flexi save option.
With the flexi save option, you can
accumulate your guaranteed income
instead of taking it as payments. Earn
loyalty additions on the accumulated
amount.
ICICI Pro Gift Select your plan for
guaranteed income and financial
security. Start your journey today.
Visit icicrolife.com
or connect with your financial advisor.